Welcome back!
欢迎回来！
Yes.
是的。
We know each other already.
我们已经认识了。
It's Mark again.
又是我，马克。
And, I have another lesson for you.
我还有另一节课给你。
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
It seems you have done a lot of lessons, with many of my colleagues.
看起来你已经上了很多课，和我的许多同事一起。
You're really motivated.
你真的很有动力。
I like it!
我喜欢这种状态！
Let's keep your learning going, and see what else you can discover.
让我们继续你的学习，看看你还能发现什么。
Today's Stoppr lesson is about another sneaky trap.
今天的Stoppr课程是关于另一个隐秘的陷阱。
Trap number 3.
陷阱三。
Sugar at work.
工作中的糖分。
Using sugar to boost your work.
用糖来提升你的工作表现。
To achieve a deadline.
为了赶上最后期限。
Reaching for sugar when you're tired at work.
在工作中感到疲惫时寻找糖分。
We've all done it.
我们都做过。
You're low on energy, a deadline is coming, and that cookie or
你精力不足，最后期限临近，那块饼干或
chocolate bar is calling your name.
巧克力正在召唤你的名字。
Let's talk about why that's a trap.
我们来谈谈为什么这是个陷阱。
Sugar gives you fast energy, yes.
糖确实能给你快速的能量，是的。
It hits quick.
它来得很快。
But it doesn't last.
但持续不了多久。
It's like lighting a match.
就像点燃火柴一样。
Bright for a second, then gone.
瞬间明亮，然后消失。
Soon after, you're yawning again.
不久之后，你又开始打哈欠。
Your focus drops.
你的注意力下降。
And guess what?
你猜怎么着？
You want more sugar.
你想要更多的糖。
Another snack, another boost.
又一个零食，又一次提升。
That's the sugar loop.
这就是糖循环。
And once you're in, it's tough to break out.
一旦进入，就很难摆脱。
It feels helpful at first.
起初感觉很有帮助。
A sweet snack, a sugary drink—it gives you a little kick.
一块甜点，一杯含糖饮料——会给你一点刺激。
Like a small push forward.
就像一个小小的推动。
But here's the truth: that push is fake.
但事实是：这种推动是假的。
It doesn't last.
它不会持久。
After the sugar rush, there's always a crash.
在糖分带来的兴奋之后，总会有崩溃。
Then what?
然后呢？
You struggle to focus.
你很难集中注意力。
You feel even more tired.
你感到更加疲惫。
Work feels harder, not easier.
工作感觉更难，而不是更容易。
So you reach for more sugar.
所以你又去吃糖。
Again.
又一次。
And again.
再一次。
It's not a snack anymore—it's a pattern.
这不再是零食——而是一个模式。
Over time, your brain links sugar to focus.
随着时间的推移，你的大脑将糖与专注联系在一起。
It starts asking for it when things get hard.
当事情变得困难时，它开始要求糖。
Not because you need it, but because it's become your habit.
不是因为你需要它，而是因为它已经成为你的习惯。
This relationship with sugar at work becomes toxic.
这种与工作中糖的关系变得有害。
It blurs the line between hunger and stress.
它模糊了饥饿和压力之间的界限。
Between fuel and escape.
在能量和逃避之间。
It tricks you into thinking you're solving a problem, when really,
它让你误以为自己在解决问题，而实际上，
you're making it worse.
你是在让情况变得更糟。
And the worst part?
最糟糕的部分是什么？
It takes your power away.
它夺走了你的力量。
Your energy, your focus—they're no longer in your hands.
你的能量，你的专注力——它们不再掌握在你手中。
Sugar runs the show.
糖掌控了一切。
But naming this trap is the first step to breaking it.
但识别这个陷阱是打破它的第一步。
You've already done that.
你已经做到了。
And that's a big deal.
这是一件大事。
That will be all for today.
今天就到这里。
I'll see you in the next lesson.
我们下节课见。
We'll keep working on your growth.
我们会继续帮助你成长。